<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Den McHenry</title>
    <link>https://denmch.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Den McHenry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 15:25:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://denmch.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Den</title>
      <link>https://denmch.github.io/about-den/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 15:25:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denmch.github.io/about-den/</guid>
      <description>I am a Front End Web Developer with the University of Washington School of Law. I&amp;rsquo;ve also worked as a one-person design and web services shop under the name Rookish Design. Fun projects Ch-ch-changes | Convert your text among any of six different styles, including camelCase (commonly used in JavaScript) and spinal-case (AKA kebab-case, commonly used in CSS).
Kompvtor | This fake &amp;ldquo;terminal&amp;rdquo; is really a demo of a custom caret (text cursor).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number Ones — 1976</title>
      <link>https://denmch.github.io/posts/number-ones-1976/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 20:14:46 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denmch.github.io/posts/number-ones-1976/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a rarity: something good that came out of Twitter. A while back somebody was tweeting about the best albums of their lifetime, one for each year they&amp;rsquo;ve been alive. I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about for probably a few months by now, and it&amp;rsquo;s been a long series of tough choices, but it&amp;rsquo;s also been rewarding and helped me to discover things I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I ever lived without.
For the year of my birth — I made the bicentennial by just a few weeks — I flirted with the Ramones, and wanted so badly to go with the Modern Lovers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Acrostic Movie List</title>
      <link>https://denmch.github.io/posts/an-acrostic-movie-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 16:03:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denmch.github.io/posts/an-acrostic-movie-list/</guid>
      <description>This popped up on Twitter a while back, and I realized I had to think about it a little bit. Then it got lost in drafts when I decided I&amp;rsquo;d rather write it up than get caught trying to craft a tweet like a nerd.
The idea is that you list a favorite movie for each letter in your name, so here goes.
 Dark City (dir. Alex Proyas, 1998) Escape from New York (dir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Not Be</title>
      <link>https://denmch.github.io/posts/people-not-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 13:07:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denmch.github.io/posts/people-not-be/</guid>
      <description>This is a brief list of certain types of conference attendees drawn from my very limited experience. It is, therefore, perfectly accurate and wholly unassailable in both its characterizations and its conclusions.
That framework’s documentation isn’t here to stand up for itself. If I don’t speak up, who will? The Advocate The speaker is still in the early stages of the talk and gives a brief description of a given technology related — but not central—to the hour’s topic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>