<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Den McHenry</title>
    <link>https://denmch.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Den McHenry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 20:14:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://denmch.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Number Ones — 1976</title>
      <link>https://denmch.github.io/posts/number-ones-1976/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 20:14:46 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denmch.github.io/posts/number-ones-1976/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a rarity: something good that came out of Twitter. A while back somebody was tweeting about the best albums of their lifetime, one for each year they&amp;rsquo;ve been alive. I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about for probably a few months by now, and it&amp;rsquo;s been a long series of tough choices, but it&amp;rsquo;s also been rewarding and helped me to discover things I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I ever lived without.
For the year of my birth — I made the bicentennial by just a few weeks — I flirted with the Ramones, and wanted so badly to go with the Modern Lovers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Acrostic Movie List</title>
      <link>https://denmch.github.io/posts/an-acrostic-movie-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 16:03:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denmch.github.io/posts/an-acrostic-movie-list/</guid>
      <description>This popped up on Twitter a while back, and I realized I had to think about it a little bit. Then it got lost in drafts when I decided I&amp;rsquo;d rather write it up than get caught trying to craft a tweet like a nerd.
The idea is that you list a favorite movie for each letter in your name, so here goes.
 Dark City (dir. Alex Proyas, 1998) Escape from New York (dir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Not Be</title>
      <link>https://denmch.github.io/posts/people-not-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 13:07:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denmch.github.io/posts/people-not-be/</guid>
      <description>This is a brief list of certain types of conference attendees drawn from my very limited experience. It is, therefore, perfectly accurate and wholly unassailable in both its characterizations and its conclusions.
That framework’s documentation isn’t here to stand up for itself. If I don’t speak up, who will? The Advocate The speaker is still in the early stages of the talk and gives a brief description of a given technology related — but not central—to the hour’s topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bundle Up Your Inbox</title>
      <link>https://denmch.github.io/posts/bundle-up-your-inbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 15:41:59 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denmch.github.io/posts/bundle-up-your-inbox/</guid>
      <description>Seven of the Best Newsletters for Front End Folks Baby, it’s cold outside, but we’ve got some excellent reading material for you. Photo credit: Matt Popovich
We may never return to those halcyon days of listservs and forums that built communities and shared knowledge in the early days of the web, but newsletters are back in vogue. The best of them perform a great function in the new, massively multi-channel social web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re Saying It Wrong</title>
      <link>https://denmch.github.io/posts/youre-saying-it-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 15:39:42 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denmch.github.io/posts/youre-saying-it-wrong/</guid>
      <description>Because my opinions are the best opinions While focusing on JavaScript to level up my web dev skills over the last several months, I’ve waged a silent war in my head over how everyone else seems to pronounce certain things.
Well, here at last is my declaration, and I will countenance no disagreement and no appeals to sensible arguments or respected authorities.
var rhymes with bear, not bar var bear = true, bar = false; tuts rhymes with boots, not butts JSON sounds like Jason, not Khe Sanh  Okay, let’s parse this … in regex/regexp, reg rhymes with leg, not ledge names ending in -ify are consciously and playfully improper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Action Movie One Liners</title>
      <link>https://denmch.github.io/posts/action-movie-one-liners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2015 15:28:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://denmch.github.io/posts/action-movie-one-liners/</guid>
      <description>When you&amp;rsquo;re the hero of an action movie, you&amp;rsquo;re going to find yourself killing — or at least subduing — people in increasingly novel ways. And you can&amp;rsquo;t do that unless you find a clever way to punctuate it.
So what should you say if you ever have to stab a bad guy in the throat with a paper clip?
I&amp;rsquo;m glad you asked, because I&amp;rsquo;ve compiled a list.
7 Things to Say in an Action Movie when Offing a Guy with a Paper Clip to the Throat  &amp;ldquo;Get clipped!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>